JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:30 PM
Dammit… Dammit it all!
I have to warn Yoshikage!
Reimi!
This picture, you took it,
right, Rohan?
Well, yes…
This one is marked
What's special about it?
HAYATO KAWAJIRI
There's a circle around
what looks like a little boy.
Oh, him…
I'm not too concerned with him.
He seemed to be sneaking around,
so I thought I'd document him.
But this boy, Hayato Kawajiri,
has the same last name
as this man here.
Huh? Really?
Look!
Definitely the same.
KOSAKU KAWAJIRI
Weren't you already
investigating him?
You're actually right.
At this rate, it's inevitable
Rohan Kishibe will find Yoshikage!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:48 PM
Hayato? Hayato!
Ugh…
Hayato, for the last time!
Now answer me!
Oh, it's you…
I could've sworn
Hayato was in there.
And look at this!
This place looks like
a bomb went off.
His clothes are
all over the hallway.
I wish he'd learn from you.
No matter how many times
I tell him, he's still a slob.
He still won't even answer me.
I'm sure he's reading manga
with his headphones on again.
Oh! Honey, you've got blood
on your fingers.
Are you okay?
I'll go get a bandage.
I-I'll take care of it myself.
I can handle a simple bandage.
Oh…
I caught my fingers in the door,
that's all.
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:50 PM
Hayato Kawajiri?
So you think this grade-school kid
EPISODE 35
BITES THE DUST, PART 1
has something to do with
Yoshikage Kira?
Well, we're not totally sure yet,
but Rohan-sensei seems to think
there's something fishy going on.
Well, yeah, I don't know
any grade schoolers
taking videos of their dad
on the down low.
That's why we're talking about
meeting up tomorrow morning
to visit Hayato Kawajiri's
house together.
Rohan-sensei said he already
figured out the address.
The jerk
sure doesn't drag his feet.
Got it. I guess I should probably
invite Okuyasu, right?
And we can't forget about Jotaro.
I'll be sure to get in touch
with Jotaro.
All right. So tomorrow at 8:30 AM.
At the intersection
with the Pepsi sign.
Got it.
8:30, huh?
I'm gonna be late for school.
But something tells me
it's gonna be worth it.
Are you okay?
I can tell something's wrong,
Sweetie…
You're all pale.
Really, it's nothing.
I just slammed my fingers
in the door.
My face shows my pain…
Now, would you please
just go make me some tea?
I'll be right down.
Of course.
I know this is going to sound
totally random,
but lately, you give off
this vibe like you'll live forever.
Well, anyway, your tea.
If anything happens to me,
you can bet your whole cover
will be blown!
Now stay the hell away
from me and my mom!
This isn't some negotiation!
You don't have a choice! Got it?!
How charming!
You think I'd ever let
someone find me out?
You of all people should've known.
Getting rid of Hayato
was the height of foolishness.
I'm trying to think of
an out right now.
It's too late now.
You did a fine job of
making it look as if
he fell and hit his head,
but your timing couldn't be worse.
Rohan Kishibe has already begun
his investigation into
Hayato Kawajiri.
They don't know for sure yet
that Kosaku Kawajiri is you,
but they're coming here tomorrow
to find out.
You mustn't remain in
this house a minute longer.
Will you stop talking…
I'm trying to think.
When things didn't go your way,
when you felt the whole world
was against you…
you'd always bite your nails
till your fingers were raw.
My poor boy.
Oh, the misery
you must be suffering.
There's no other way now.
You must leave this town behind
for good, Yoshikage.
You still have a chance to escape
and hold on to your anonymity.
You want me to run away
and abandon Morioh?
I'm sick to death of living
in the shadow of fear,
of living every moment
in excruciating secrecy…
you know that!
I swear I will never
leave this town.
What?!
The arrow just moved on its own!
I didn't do anything!
I wasn't even touching it!
Th-The arrow…
Y-Yoshikage!
Hayato! Hayato?!
JULY 16TH (FRI) 7:30 AM
Just how long are you going
to stay sleeping, Hayato?
It's time to get up and—
What, you're already
awake? You startled me.
Hayato, breakfast.
Geez, you could at least
try to answer…
I had a terrible
night's sleep last night.
He found out I was a witness
in one of his murders.
For now, I've made sure
he can't lay a finger
on me or Mom, but…
That'll work for only so long…
I-I don't understand…
What's gotten into you, Yoshikage?
You've been acting strange
since last night.
Don't ignore me, Yoshikage!
I don't know why,
but Rohan Kishibe is now keen on
snooping around Hayato Kawajiri!
They're coming to search
the house tomorrow
There's no cause for alarm.
B-But, Yoshikage!
Deadly Queen has
acquired a third ability
I… I don't understand.
What happened that
you can be so lackadaisical?
-MORIOH'S FAMOUS-
MISO-MARINATED COW TONGUE
Miso-marinated cow tongue.
What? You're kidding!
We're on the air?
Er, um… It's 7:55, time for
today's prefectural weather report.
Today we can enjoy sunny skies.
Hayato! Hey, Hayato!
Could you answer the phone…
Ever since that bath last night,
he's changed.
What the hell happened?
Hayato! Please answer the phone!
CRASH
My favorite china tea set!
This is your fault!
Why do you always ignore me?!
Fine! So I'm just
a nuisance to you, huh?!
Then I'll just stay
out of your way!
Now, now. Let's not start
the day off with an argument.
If it can't be fixed,
I'll just buy you another one.
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
No, I'm afraid not.
Wrong number, of course.
Hayato's just going through
a quiet phase.
We're a family,
we should support each other,
not tear each other down.
Support each other, okay.
Well, I suppose I should
get going to work.
I wonder if a certain someone
will allow me
to give her a goodbye kiss?
Huh?
Have a wonderful day…
So he left…
I'm right here, son.
Why don't you let me keep you
company for part of the way?
One moment,
I'm on top of the world,
the next,
I'm in the depths of depression…
So much has happened.
It's been a whirlwind of emotion.
But now I will be able to live
a life free of worry and anxiety.
You really put the pressure on
last night,
but you brought out the best in me…
I matured.
You were so
extraordinarily determined.
Imagine that, you actually
threatened the Yoshikage Kira…
Y- Yoshikage Kira?
Oops, I guess I just
told you my name.
So, does this mean
you're gonna kill me after all?
Kill you?
Because you now know my secret?
I've no need to go down that road.
I've matured.
Nothing you or anyone else
tries to do matters any more…
I am now unrivaled.
You no longer arouse
any interest in me.
Besides, if I wanted to kill you…
I would have done so
a long time ago last night.
We are all going to
get along just fine.
So breathe easy.
I'm your dad and you are my son.
Well, Daddy dearest
must head to the station.
Do your best at school today,
Hayato.
Unrivaled…
He chose the word unrivaled.
Which means there must be others
with the same kind of weird powers.
But his confidence is terrifying…
So he says he's unrivaled now.
Does that mean he gained
some new power?
What should I do?
I have no idea
what I'm supposed to do.
You're…
Hayato Kawajiri,
am I right?
DEADLY QUEEN
JULY 16TH (FRI) 8:24 AM
I've been waiting for you.
My name is Rohan Kishibe.
I have to say I'm very curious
about something.
It's about this picture.
This is you, right?
And were you taking video
of your dad in the back there?
Wait.
What… is this?
I know that was unexpected…
Questioning him
would be so troublesome.
Reading Hayato Kawajiri's mind
is much more efficient.
Not to mention,
much more accurate too.
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
Huh? Why would that appear?
The only thing Heaven's Door
should be revealing
is a candid, honest written account
of this boy's life memories.
And yet… a warning?
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
What the hell is going on?
Is this "warning" part of
his experience?
I wasn't planning on giving
this boy more than a quick peruse,
but he's got me strangely hooked.
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
"Do not read on"?
Who could this be for?
AN OLD GUY WALKED BY
WITH HIS FLY DOWN.
HE SNEEZED,
THEN EXCLAIMED, "DAMMIT."
A WOMAN CHUCKLED.
W-What is this?
This is making less and less sense.
What does all this mean?
Dammit.
Who is this kid?
IT RAINED.
Darn, the weather report
never said anything about rain!
AT 8:27 AM, LIGHTNING STRUCK
ABOVE THE PEPSI SIGN.
8:27…
Who is this Hayato Kawajiri?
How could he experience the future?
Is he another Stand user?
No… This wouldn't make sense
as a Stand ability.
Heaven's Door reveals only
what a person has actually
seen and heard.
The explanation should be
somewhere in here…
DAD ISN'T REALLY DAD.
HE MADE SOME GUY AND GIRL
BLOW UP WITHOUT A TRACE AT
AN APARTMENT NEAR JOZENJI.
HE'S A BLOOD-THIRSTY MURDERER.
I DISCOVERED HIS TRUE IDENTITY.
HE HAS SUPER-HUMAN POWER.
MY DAD'S NAME IS YOSHIKAGE KIRA
YOSHIKAGE KIRA
Kira…
I got it!
This kid is the jackpot!
I finally found him!
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri!
He's disguised himself
as this kid's father!
THEN ROHAN KISHIBE WAS KILLED.
THE NEW, SUPERPOWERED KIRA
MURDERED HIM.
Then Rohan Kishibe was killed?
The new, superpowered Kira
murdered him…
Deadly Queen, bomb type three,
Bites the Dust.
Heaven's Door!
Rohan Kishibe, Deadly Queen
has already entered your pupil!
Your visual perception
isn't deceiving you!
Deadly Queen's bomb type three
has already been activated!
Deadly Queen's new power…
will annihilate all
who attempt to take me down!
It's a bomb that will
activate in anyone
who dares approach Hayato
to get to me.
THEN ROHAN KISHIBE WAS KILLED.
Hayato's verbalizing
of my true name
will also activate the bomb,
as will putting my name in writing.
In other words,
I've planted the bomb on Hayato!
I just remembered…
I promised I'd meet Koichi
and the gang here at 8:30…
I finally… discovered
Yoshikage Kira's true identity…
Koichi'll be here any minute.
I have to tell him…
I… I finally… found him…
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri.
Heaven's Door found him.
I have to tell…
Koichi…
And now,
gaze upon the glory that is
Deadly Queen, bomb type three!
K-Koichi!
Was I dreaming?
I had a terrible night's sleep
last night.
It was one horrible dream
after another…
Hayato!
Just how long are you going to
stay sleeping, Hayato?
It's time to get up and—
What, you're already awake?
You startled me.
Hayato, breakfast.
Geez, you could at least
try to answer…
This… there's no question…
What? You're kidding!
- We're on the air?
- The morning news…
Hayato! Hey, Hayato!
Could you answer the phone.
Th-This isn't a dream…
None of that was a dream.
Th-This is the same morning.
It's repeating…
I'm reliving yesterday's morning!
Yoshikage Kira…
His name is Yoshikage Kira!
He's behind all this!
This is what he meant
by being unrivaled,
he's done something to me
with his new power!
Hayato! Please answer the phone!
Oh, yeah!
Look out—
Ow…
Nice catch. It's like you knew
it was going to fall.
But if your ears are still working,
try answering me next time!
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
- Huh? No, it's not.
- So I'm the only one who knows
this morning has
happened already.
It's like you knew
it was going to fall, huh?
It appears you've returned
from a long day of
blasting your friend
to kingdom come, Hayato.
To tell you the truth,
I actually do not know
the exact details
of your little foray.
This type of Deadly Queen power
is called Bites the Dust,
it automatically protects me…
from inside your body, Hayato.
I wonder if you are aware
that I killed you last night?
As if someone up there had
witnessed the despair
eating at my heart,
I received a gift, a new ability.
I tried the ability out on you,
and time reversed course one hour.
The reality that I had murdered you
was no more.
You also became my personal
life-protecting bomb.
You told one of them about me,
thereby activating the bomb and
transporting yourself back here.
So who did you annihilate, hm?
You can tell me.
Who did you murder?
I-I didn't tell anyone…
Of course! Then someone
must have interrogated you.
That would be Rohan Kishibe.
Even if spilling the beans
never crosses your mind,
a simple inquiry about yours truly
is enough to activate
Bites the Dust.
Then, of course, you incinerate
your target and zip back here.
Your visit with Rohan Kishibe
is now just a figment
of your imagination!
Now you know how Deadly Queen's
Bites the Dust works.
My name will never leave your lips.
No soul will ever live
to seek my identity!
EPISODE 36
BITES THE DUST, PART 2